▍2026 美网 男单第一轮
贝雷蒂尼 7-6⁴ 7-6³ 6-0 瓦林卡 · 赛后告别仪式
wonderful memories
太多美好的回忆
and I'm sure an emotional moment for you.
此刻你一定百感交集
Yeah, it is.
是的，确实
First, congrats Mateo and your team
首先，恭喜马特奥和你的团队
to the Grand Slam.
在这个大满贯
It was a two time good match.
这是一场好球
I wish you the best for the rest
祝你在往后的生涯
of your career and this tournament.
和这项赛事里一切顺利
Congrats. But for me,
恭喜你。而对我来说
it's been more than 20 years
已经过去二十多年了
since the first time I came here in New York.
从我第一次来到纽约算起
It was I remember
我记得很清楚
when I played the quali the first year,
第一年我打的是资格赛
it was impressive for me
那种感觉太震撼了
to to feel the New York vibes,
感受纽约的气息
the the energy of this tournament.
感受这项赛事的能量
But over the year,
这些年里
I received so much support,
我得到了太多支持
so much love because of you.
太多的爱，都来自你们
So, I really enjoy that.
我真的很享受
I find a way how to play my best here.
我在这里打出了最好的网球
It was it was always really special.
这里永远都很特别
And tonight again was one
今晚又一次证明
of the reason why I kept playing until 41
这就是我打到41岁的原因之一
is to leave those moments like you gave me
就是为了留下今晚这样的时刻
tonight like you gave us tonight.
你们今晚给了我，给了我们
Amazing support.
这样的支持太棒了
Oh, thank you so much.
真的非常感谢
Even I went back to Switzerland
我甚至已经回了瑞士
and I came back.
然后又飞了回来
I would like to thanks the tournament
我要感谢赛事
for the wild card because for me
给了我这张外卡
to have this opportunity to finish here
因为能在这里收尾
was was really meaningful for myself.
对我个人意义重大
So I'm super grateful
所以我无比感激
to have received the wild card
能拿到这张外卡
because it was something important
因为这件事很重要
for me to have the opportunity
它让我有机会
to finish the four Grand Slam here
在这里打完这四个大满贯
in New York 10 years after winning.
在纽约，在我夺冠10年之后
I'm going to miss it for sure.
我一定会想念它
I'm going to miss it big time.
会非常非常想念
But I'm... Thank you.
但我……谢谢你们
Thank you.
谢谢
I love I love the game so much
我太爱这项运动了
that I really try to push until my own limit
所以我一直把自己逼到极限
and this year it is my own limit.
而今年，就是我的极限
So I really want to thank you all
所以我真的想谢谢你们所有人
for all those years,
谢谢这么多年
all those support was really amazing.
这些支持真的太了不起了
ladies and gentlemen to mark this occasion.
女士们先生们，为纪念这一刻
Please welcome Craig Tiley,
有请克雷格·泰利
CEO of the USTA, and Eric Butorac,
美国网协CEO，以及布托拉克
US Open tournament director
美网赛事总监
to present Stan
他们将为斯坦
with a very special memento
送上一份特别的纪念品
for this occasion.
以纪念此刻